<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alchemy Of Creatures</string>
    <string name="rule">
        Rules
    </string>
    <string name="rule_text">Combine two magical creatures to get a new species. The creatures are divided into dark and light. Get all kinds of creatures and unlock new journal entries about the history of the sorcerer. As you get closer to your goal, you will get bonuses and achivas. Good luck on this challenging but exciting path!</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="en">En</string>
    <string name="ru">Ru</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">off</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dear_diary1">Dear Diary,\n\nToday I have decided to begin a great and dangerous task - I am going to restore the magical beings that have almost disappeared from our world. As a sorcerer\'s apprentice, I have always dreamed of restoring the magical order that was once our reality. But every year, more and more magical beings disappear due to wars and conflicts in human territory.\n\nThese creatures once helped us maintain the magical order, but now that order is broken and the magic is disappearing along with these wonderful creatures. I have decided that this cannot continue, and I must do something to save our world from the complete disappearance of magic.\n\nMy first goal is to restore the dragons. Dragons were once a symbol of power</string>
    <string name="dear_diary2">and wisdom, but now there are almost none left. I will begin research that will help me restore their population. It will be dangerous, but I\'m sure it\'s possible.\n\nLikewise, I\'m going to work on restoring other magical creatures - phoenixes, griffins, elementals, and many others. I know it will be difficult, but I can\'t afford to just sit back and watch our world lose magic.\n\nI am willing to risk my life to bring magic and harmony back to our world. And I\'ll keep you posted on the whole process, dear diary. Perhaps someday this story will become the legend of how one sorcerer\'s apprentice changed the world. \n</string>
    <string name="chapter2_1">Chapter 2: In Search of the Dragon Egg

Dear Diary,

My research has begun, and the first step was to find the dragon egg. This was not an easy task, for dragons have become rare and few people know where they can be found. However, through my knowledge and contacts in the magical world, I was able to get information on the possible location of the dragon egg.

My first goal was to find the ancient caves where legends say ancient dragons dwelt. I set out on my journey, armed with magical artifacts that would help protect me from the dangers that might await me in these forbidden places.
The journey was difficult and dangerous. I encountered various obstacles, including traps guarded by magical guards and even creatures that tried to thwart my quest. But with my knowledge and experience, I was able to overcome all the difficulties.</string>

    <string name="chapter2_2">Finally, I found a cave that seemed forgotten by time. In its depths I discovered an ancient nesting nook, where a single dragon egg lay. My joy was endless - this was the first step towards the recovery of the dragons.

Now it was up to me to return to safety and begin the process of incubating this precious egg. It will be a daunting task, but I am determined and confident of success. I know this is only the beginning of my great venture, but I am willing to go through the hardships for the great goal of bringing magic back to our world.

I will continue to keep you updated on all developments, dear diary. My story is just beginning, and I hope that one day it will become legendary
</string>


    <string name="chapter3_1">Chapter 3: In Search of Ancient Knowledge

Dear Diary,

My research for ways to restore dragons led me to ancient texts and artifacts stored in forgotten places. I set out on a journey in search of ancient knowledge of dragons, and my efforts were rewarded.

I discovered an ancient scroll that contained information on rituals that could attract dragons back to our world. However, to perform these rituals, I would need to gather rare ingredients that can only be found in the most dangerous and mysterious places.

My next quest is to travel through forbidden lands to find these ingredients. I must be prepared to face dangers and challenges, but I am determined to overcome all obstacles for the sake of restoring the dragons.
</string>

    <string name="chapter3_2">
        In addition to this, I have begun researching other ways to restore magical creatures. I turned to old scrolls about phoenixes, griffins, and elementals to find the keys to reviving them. My research has taken a long time, but each new piece of information brings me closer to my goal.

My dedication to this cause has not waned, and I am willing to accept any challenge to bring magic back to our world. I know the path before me will be difficult, but I am determined and hopeful.

    </string>

    <string name="chapter4_1">
        Chapter 4: Journey to the forbidden lands

My research led me to the decision to travel through forbidden lands in search of rare ingredients needed to perform the revival rituals of ancient creatures. My road lay through dangerous and mysterious places, home to creatures of which little is known.

I gathered my supplies, including maps and amulets of protection, and set off. My first stop was the Forest of Shadows, a place where legend has it that ancient forest spirits dwell. This forest was known for its mystical atmosphere and the dangerous traps the spirits set to protect their secrets.

    </string>

    <string name="chapter4_2">
        Overcoming the hardships of the Forest of Shadows, I traveled to the Valley of Evening Mist, where it was rumored to be possible to find a rare flower that was one of the key ingredients for the ancient creatures revival ritual. The valley was shrouded in mist and filled with strange sounds that caused anxiety in my heart. But I continued my journey in spite of this.

After obtaining a few ingredients, I headed towards the Mountains of Eternal Ice. This place was known for its ice caves and the ancient ice monsters living there. But I was up for the challenge and was able to obtain another rare ingredient.

    </string>

    <string name="chapter5_1">
        Chapter 5: Return to the magic academy

After a long journey through the forbidden lands, I returned to the magic academy with the ingredients I had gathered. I was to perform a ritual to revive ancient creatures that had been lost centuries ago. My teachers and students at the academy were eagerly awaiting my return, and I was ready to share my discoveries with them.

After preparing everything I needed, I began the rebirth ritual. Using ancient spells and gathered ingredients, I was able to summon ancient beings from the depths of time.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter5_2">
        It was a powerful and exciting moment as ancient magical monsters that had been lost to the world for centuries emerged before me.

My teachers and students were amazed by the sight, and I felt that my mission had been accomplished. Now that I have learned how to restore ancient creatures, I can pass on my knowledge and skills to the next generation of mages. Magic will once again come alive in our world thanks to the revived monsters and the new knowledge I brought from the forbidden lands.

    </string>

    <string name="chapter6_1">
        Chapter 6: Doubts

Despite the joy and satisfaction I felt at the success of the rebirth ritual, I was plagued by doubts. The revival of ancient beings, including those who were known for their evil and destructive powers, made me question the rightness of my choice.

I asked myself: was it right for me to revive not only good magical beings, but evil ones as well? Could I be sure that these creatures would not bring destruction and suffering to our world? Might my thirst for knowledge and my desire to restore ancient monsters lead to unpredictable consequences?

I spent a lot of time pondering these questions. I realized that my mission to recover forgotten magic might have its dark sides.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter6_2">
        However, I also saw an opportunity to use the knowledge and power of these creatures for good rather than evil.

Thus, I decided that my purpose was not only to restore ancient beings, but also to train them to use their magical abilities to protect and help others. I was to teach them goodness so that they would become allies in the struggle for harmony and well-being in our world.

    </string>

    <string name="chapter7_1">
        Chapter 7: New Challenges

In recent months, I have been able to bring back many magical creatures to our world that had been forgotten for centuries. However, despite my best efforts, the balance in the world is still not restored. There are still many creatures that remain outside our world, and I realize that my mission is far from complete.

In order to bring back the remaining creatures, I will need to deepen my knowledge of ancient rituals and magical spells.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter7_2">
        I must study artifacts and scrolls that contain information on how to bridge the boundaries between worlds and bring back those lost in time and space.

In addition, I realize that I will need to find allies who share my goal and are willing to help me in this difficult endeavor. Together, we can create powerful spells and rituals that can penetrate the boundaries of worlds and bring back those who have been lost.


    </string>
    <string name="chapter8_1">
Chapter 8: Doubt

That day, as I was delving into the study of the ancient scrolls, one of my students came to me. He stood before me with a noble look and a timid expression on his face.

"Master," he began, "I have seen you bring magical beings back to our world, and I want to help you in this endeavor. Allow me to become your assistant and accompany you on this difficult journey."

I looked at him in surprise. My disciple was gravely ill, his face was pale and his eyes were tired. I knew he had already been through a lot in his life, and I doubted whether he could endure all the trials that awaited us on our journey.

"My apprentice," I said, "I appreciate your determination and desire to help. But this assignment will be dangerous and arduous, and I am worried about your health. I'm not sure you'll be able to endure all the trials that await us."

The apprentice lowered his head, but then raised it again, the fire of determination burning in his eyes.


    </string>
 <string name="chapter8_2">
     Master, he said emphatically, "I know it will be difficult, but I want to be useful. Let me help you in this endeavor. I am willing to accept all risks."I saw the sincerity in his eyes and realized that he would not back down from his decision. I wondered. Maybe he really could be useful. But I still doubted if I should take him up on his offer. "Give me time to think about it," I said finally. "Ill think about your offer and make a decision." The apprentice nodded and walked away, leaving me alone with my thoughts. I knew I needed to make a decision soon. Perhaps the apprentice could be my trusted ally, but I had to make sure he wouldnt put his life in danger.

 </string>

    <string name="chapter9_1">
Chapter 9: Sacrifice and Healing

My doubts never left me. I was worried about my apprentice, his health was fragile and I didnt want to jeopardize his life. But that day, when we went to search for the last magical creature, my apprentice got much worse.

He was losing strength with every step, but he refused to stop. We kept moving forward, searching for a way to bring the magical creature back to our world. The apprentice was persistent, but his condition was getting worse by the minute.

When we finally reached the location of the last magical creature, the apprentice could barely stand on his feet. He was struggling to breathe, but despite that, he continued to help me find a way to retrieve the creature.

    </string>
<string name="chapter9_2">
    Suddenly, the disciple fell to his knees, exhausted by the sickness. I was willing to sacrifice my own strength to help him, but he refused to accept my help. At the last moment, when I was ready to use my magic to heal him, one of the previously rescued dragons approached him.

The dragon radiated light and warmth, and his eyes shone like stars. He raised his paws and placed them on his apprentice. We watched as the light enveloped the disciple and his face was filled with new strength and life. The dragon granted the disciple healing.

</string>

    <string name="chapter10_1">
        Chapter 10: The world is saved

Thus began our adventure. We faced many trials and dangers, but thanks to my students perseverance and determination, we were able to overcome all difficulties. Together we brought magical creatures back to our world and made it a better place.

    </string>
    <string name="chapter10_2">
        My student has shown himself as a true hero, and I am most proud of him. Our cooperation became not only a source of help, but also inspiration for me. Together, we were able to accomplish incredible things. This story will become a legend.
    </string>
    <string name="sound_is_already_on">Sound is already on</string>
    <string name="sound_is_off_now">Sound is off now</string>
    <string name="sound_is_already_off">Sound is already off</string>
    <string name="sound_is_on_now">Sound is on now</string>
    <string name="new_creature_unlocked">New creature unlocked!</string>
    <string name="creature_already_unlocked">Creature already unlocked!</string>

</resources>